<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PLUME: My friends, after much debate, we have decided we must abandon this tower, and move our work to the other islands of this planet.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: The interior of our dwelling has rapidly taken on a quantum nature after prolonged exposure to the roaming quantum shard. As much as it pains me, I fear it will only become increasingly unfeasible to continue living within this space.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PLUME: Does anyone have any proposals for which island we should move our settlement to?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: We should return to the island we arrived on our first expedition! The height of the island's cliffs offers the most protection from the ocean's waves, and the interior provides a calm space to work.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		THATCH: I believe one of the other islands would also be suitable site to construct a larger site for building more advanced projects as well!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		THATCH: Of note: this second island sails along the same direction as the planet's orbit around the sun - making its days about three times longer than one would experience on the other island.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>	
	<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: On the other apphendage, this would reduce the frequency of being immersed by passing tides, which would be favorable for a site of construction!
		</Text>
			</TextBlock>



	<ShipLogConditions>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC_P EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>2</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC_P EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC_P EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>8</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>