<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	

	<![CDATA[<i>Excavation Site</i>]]>
	

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>
			COLEUS: Thanks to Melorae's new quantum rule, we should at last be able to reach the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Quantum Moon's</color>]]> surface without its clouds obscuring our sight and allowing it to slip back into superposition.</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			MELORAE: In addition, with the discovery that the tentacled species are drawn to the surface of Giant's Deep by the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Quantum Moon's</color>]]> gravity, we have even been able to calculate the moon's physical mass through its gravitational forces!</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			THATCH: Plume, are you sure you do not wish to join us on this expedition? This expedition to the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Quantum Moon</color>]]> could bring us closer to our goals than ever before.</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
			PLUME: I am sure. I must stay behind to take care of Phlox, but I wish you all well, my friends. I shall watch your expedition from afar with bated respiration!</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
			COLEUS: Oh, but Plume, if you wish to watch our expedition, the thick clouds here on Giant's Deep will surely completely obscure your sight of our shuttle!</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: I suggest visiting the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Quantum Moon locator</color>]]> on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Ember Twin's</color>]]> south pole instead. With the locator's assistance, you would have a clear view of which planet the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Quantum Moon</color>]]> is orbiting at all times!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: In addition, a set of eyes at the locator would help us greatly in locking the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Quantum Moon</color>]]> in orbit around a specific planet, allowing us more eyes to calculate a shuttle trajectory to our destination!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: That would be a wise idea, Thatch. Phlox and I will gladly serve as your set of eyes from afar; Be curious on your journey, my friends!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC_G R4</FactID>
			<Condition>2</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC_G R5</FactID>
			<Condition>2</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC_G EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC_G EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>2</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC_G EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>3</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SF Jelly EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>3</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SF Jelly EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>3</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SF Jelly EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>3</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>