<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">

<![CDATA[<i>solely</i>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PHLOX: Papa! My sand dwelling was toppled by the waves again!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: Why does the ocean hate my sand dwellings? Are they not good enough, papa?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: The ocean means no harm towards your lovely little dwellings, my dear Phlox. Perhaps you might be building them too close to the shoreline?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: But papa, it's easier to build with the damp sand.. And I build them further and further up each day, but the ocean always seems to follow! The ocean is so mean!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: I apologize on its behalf, my dear Phlox. But like the universe, the ocean is - and we are. It bears no conscious thought, nor ill will against us.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: Papa, could you ask the universe to be less mean?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: I will.. do my best. But in the meantime, would you like to sculpt something with papa instead? What would you like to sculpt today?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: Yes, let's sculpt instead! Could we sculpt a miniature of the Looming City? Papa's dwellings always look so incredibly cool!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: Of course! That would make papa very happy indeed. And Phlox: papa is sure that someday, you'll grow up to be an even better architect than him!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>