<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Concluding findings on experiment regarding effect of water on deadly matter: <![CDATA[<color=orange>matter remains in prevalently high and unchanged concentrations,</color>]]> even after prolonged immersion of the island's capsized surface.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Disappointingly, water only temporarily displaces the matter, and has no lasting effect on the matter.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Although it may not offer a lasting solution to the matter, this discovery, at least, provides a possible answer to the greatest question that has been weighing on my mind.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: If the deadly matter is unable to penetrate water - unable to <![CDATA[<i>harm</i>]]> those underwater, I must infer it was why I alone was spared what happened to our clan, aboard the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Deep Storm Station.</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Extrapolating from this conclusion, this property also explains how several species of the star system's native species dwelling underwater have survived as well.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: <![CDATA[<i>A terrifying realization has just struck me.</i>]]> Oh, I can only offer my immense gratitude for the planet's thick atmosphere obscuring it completely from my sight - or I could have invited them to a similar fate...
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Of note to self: I must be careful to NEVER <![CDATA[<color=orange>lock the Quantum Moon in orbit around Giant's Deep for any extended period,</color>]]> to keep them safe from this terrible danger.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>FlipIsland EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>FlipIsland EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>7</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>