<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		DAZ: Good day, Ramie! How are you doing?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		RAMIE: Goodness! You're too bright to look directly at, standing in the sun like that, Daz! Why are you so shiny? What do you have coated on your exterior?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		DAZ: <![CDATA[<i>And where's your suit?!</i]]> How are you walking around on the surface of Ember Twin exposed like that? Did Cassava invent some unbelievably strong and lustrous sunscreen, composed of his love for you?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		DAZ: <![CDATA[<i>Hah!</i]]> An amusing guess, Ramie, but does my complexion not appear familiar? I am currently composed of alloy projected from a projection pool!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		RAMIE: Oh? I hadn't noticed!! Does that mean you've invented a new type of projection stone that allows us to wander freely outside the range of the pool, Daz? I am awestruck! Have you come up with a name for this new stone yet?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		DAZ: I am flattered, my friend. And yes, Cassava came up with one: the <![CDATA[<color=orange>voyager stone!</color>]]> Named after the thalassic planet it was conceived on, it will take us on many incredible voyages across the star system!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		RAMIE: That's a shame. I was about to propose it be named the sightless stone - I will soon lose mine if I continue staring at your alloy vessel! I eagerly look forward to being able to use your voyager stones one day, my dear friend.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
</NomaiObject>