<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		DAZ: Has anyone seen my projection stone to <![CDATA[<color=orange>Lovers' Cove?</color>]]> I cannot seem to locate it anywhere!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Ah, I may have overheard Mallow mentioning Avens burying a projection stone away to hide an embarrassing conversation he had with you.. I have never seen your brother and his spouse so deeply embarrassed!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: <![CDATA[<i>What?!</i>]]> I had thought he meant that jokingly! Is Avens under the impression that projection stones instantaneously come into existence on their own?!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: Moreover, has my brother forgotten conversations shared across projection stones are <![CDATA[<color=orange>recorded into the projection boards they are written on,</color>]]> and not physically stored in the projection stones themselves?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		DAZ: Furthermore! Projection stones grant Nomai <![CDATA[<color=orange>access to all conversations written through that stone</color>]]> stored within <![CDATA[<color=orange>each corresponding whiteboard,</color>]]> not just conversations to my whiteboard! This is quite inconsiderate of them!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<LocationB />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Oh, to be so gelatinous your brother could forget how projection stones work... I'll try to press Mallow to return the stone to you soon, my love.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Workshop EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>4</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Workshop EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>