<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PLUME: Friends on the Hanging City, I seek your attention.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: The interior of our dwelling is rapidly taking on a quantum nature after prolonged exposure to the quantum shard. It is with a heavy heart that I, and the rest of the survey team, have decided to abandon the Looming City.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PLUME: In the interest of safety and practicality, we will be moving our work to the islands along Giant's Deep's equator. The storm shelters engineered by Kousa can be put to good use to protect us from cyclones beyond this space.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		KOUSA: These news sadden me, but I know it pains you most of all, Plume. We all know how hard you worked to build this tower to house our friends.. Perhaps we will find another use for this structure in the future.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: Melorae had a brilliant idea to that end. We could repurpose this structure into a space to teach our younglings about the quantum rules, to foster their curiosity and appreciation for our history and this star system.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		BELLS: What a lovely idea! I hear young Phlox has already become a master of <![CDATA[<color=orange>quantum entanglement</color>]]> using the Looming City's quantum shard. I would be honored to be part of this project to teach and inspire our future generations!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>	
	<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		BELLS: On the other appendage, I now fear for the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Tower of Quantum Knowledge,</color>]]> which was built under Brittle Hollow's own quantum shard.. How likely is this shard to invade our tower, as the one within the Looming Tower did, Plume?
		</Text>
			</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>	
	<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: I shall plunge that whole piece of Brittle Hollow into the black hole if that quantum shard even begins to think of it! It will <![CDATA[<i>not</i>]]> invade my precious Hanging City!
		</Text>
			</TextBlock>


	<ShipLogConditions>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC_P EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>2</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC_P EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC_P EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>8</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>