<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		AVENS: Oh, Daz! I would posit with certainty you were not expecting visitors today... Your workshop is a <![CDATA[<i>mess!</i>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		DAZ: Oh, goodness! When did you arrive here, Avens?! Er, I will not be taking input at this time regarding the state of my workshop. The mark of a hard worker is a messy workplace!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		AVENS: I would never dispute your workaholism, my dear brother - but goodness, you <![CDATA[<i>must</i>]]> try to keep organized! How would you even know which of these scrolls have been formatted already? Allow me to lend you an appendage.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		DAZ: I have an intuitive sense while working. So many scrolls are delivered to be formatted and recycled. Oh - do not leave that scroll there, please! A cyclone could sweep it into the seas while beyond the gravity pod's range.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		AVENS: How have you been, Daz? How is Cassava? I heard the two of you would not be joining us at the Deep Storm Station on the day of the test. Is there.. an important reason for your absence, if I may indulge my curiosity?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		DAZ: Oh, um.. Yes, there is. Please, do not tell anyone else about this, but... I'm planning to ask for Cassava's appendage in marriage at the moment of the test. I wish to spend the day setting up the perfect mood for this surprise!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		AVENS: <![CDATA[<i>Oh my!</i>]]> Do you mean that, Daz? Do you plan to use... Oh, but for what reason?! Cassava is already soundly in love with you, Daz! I am sure he would accept your appendage without pause!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		DAZ: I.. I can't be sure! ..And besides, I can't let the chance to have the first <![CDATA[<color=orange>time-traveling marriage</color>]]> slip by!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
</NomaiObject>