<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		LAEVI: Are you scared, Taget? I can't believe it. We're finally going to get to play the anglerfish game with a real anglerfish...
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		LAMI: We have nothing to fear! I even brought a <![CDATA[<color=orange>distress beacon</color>]]> on the invisible chance we might need assistance. Just remember Aunt Pye's lessons and be brave, friends!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		TAGET: I.. I can hear its breathing echoing terrifyingly through this tiny seed... I want to at least leave this recording of our last moments behind, just in case.. in case... we mess up.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		LAEVI: Do you think the anglerfish inside is as large as the fossil we're standing on? Maybe the one inside hasn't come after us even with all the noise we're making, because it thinks the larger one here is still alive.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		TAGET: I h-hope not. The chamber inside the large seed isn't very spacious, so if the anglerfish is too big, we might not be able to sneak around it at all..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		TAGET: Wait! Could.. couldn't it have other senses we don't know about then, if it can sense its own dead..? The only information we have is from a hypothesis studying a long-dead fossil. I feel increasingly fearful about our odds of survival..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>	
	<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		LAMI: That's enough rumination, Taget! This is our chance to send a message to another clan, and do something even the adults are scared to do!
		</Text>
			</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>	
	<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		LAMI: HEAR US, ANGLERFISH! THE NOMAI ARE NOT AFRAID OF YOU! 
		</Text>
			</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>	
	<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		TAGET: No, no no no... I-it just roared.. It's.. it's AWAKE! I am aborting this mission!!
		</Text>
		</TextBlock>
</NomaiObject>