<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PLUME: Friends on the Hanging City, I seek your attention. We have decided we must abandon the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Looming City.</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: The interior of our dwelling has rapidly taken on a quantum nature after prolonged exposure to the roaming quantum shard. I fear it will only become increasingly impossible to continue living within this space.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		PLUME: We plan to return to the island we arrived on during our first expedition to construct a new settlement there, as the height of the island's cliffs offers the most protection from visiting tides.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		FILIX: These news sadden me, but I know it pains you most of all, Plume. We all know how hard you worked to build this tower to house our friends.. Perhaps we will find another use for this structure in the future.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: Melorae had a brilliant idea to that end. We could repurpose this structure into a space to teach our younglings about the quantum rules, to foster their curiosity and appreciation for our history and this star system.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		BELLS: I hear young Phlox has already become a master of <![CDATA[<color=orange>quantum entanglement</color>]]> using the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Looming City's quantum shard.</color>]]> I would be honored to be part of this project to teach and inspire our future generations, Plume.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>	
	<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		THATCH: I must admit: I shall miss the relative peace and quiet on this island. I never imagined we would return to the islands outside, tossed by cyclones and storms!
		</Text>
			</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>	
	<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: Have courage, Thatch. The <![CDATA[<color=orange>storm shelters</color>]]> Kousa engineered will protect us from cyclones beyond this space. We shall face the storms together, without fear!
		</Text>
			</TextBlock>


	<ShipLogConditions>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC_P EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>2</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC_P EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC_P EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>8</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>