<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	

	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: Greetings, and gratitude for listening to my report! Today, I'm doing a report called <![CDATA[<color=orange>"Tidal Forces on Giant's Deep"!</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: Ok, um! To start: Gravity is the force that pulls things down towards the center of mass of the thing the gravity comes from.</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: On a planet, gravity makes things fall down. Giant's Deep has lots of gravity, which makes falling hurt really bad. But on a bigger scale, everything in the star system is being pulled by the sun, causing them to orbit around it.</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: As a planet orbits the sun, the side of the planet facing the sun is pulled more towards the sun's gravity. Solid things don't feel this difference very much - but since water is more flowy, it can be pulled way more.</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: On a giant ocean planet like Giant's Deep, the sun <![CDATA[<color=orange>creates higher tides on the side of the ocean facing it.</color>]]> We call these tides "solar tides".</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: But the sun is still really far away, which makes this pull pretty weak. At least, compared to the tidal forces a <![CDATA[<color=orange>moon</color>]]> causes on a planet!</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: When it visits Giant's Deep, since it's so much closer, the Quantum Moon pulls the near side of the ocean facing it, <![CDATA[<i>and</i>]]> pushes the far side out too - <![CDATA[<color=orange>causing high tides on both sides!</color>]]> We call these tides, lunar tides!</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: So what happens when the Quantum Moon and the sun both <![CDATA[<color=orange>align in orbit?</color>]]> Their combined pulling creates the highest tides possible on the ocean, so high they can <![CDATA[<color=orange>almost submerge whole islands</color>]]> along the equator of the planet!</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: Even if <![CDATA[<color=orange>the Quantum Moon is on the other side of the planet from the sun</color>]]> when it happens, this alignment will still happen because of the moon's tidal forces on both side of the planet!</Text>
	</TextBlock>
<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: The sun and moon eclipse when they align during this alignment. That's why we call this highest tide, the <![CDATA[<color=orange>sunless tide!</color>]]></Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PHLOX: In conclusion, gravity from the sun and the visiting Quantum Moon cause tidal forces that cause the ocean to rise and fall! That concludes my presentation. My gratitude for all your attention!</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>12</ID>
		<ParentID>11</ParentID>
		<Text>
			PLUME: What a marvellous report and presentation, Phlox! Now I understand why you wanted to visit each island with us recently.. But I am curious: why did you suddenly want to make a report about tides?</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>
		<ID>13</ID>
		<ParentID>12</ParentID>
		<Text>
			PHLOX: Because the ocean kept destroying my sand dwellings that I made to show you! Filix suggested I study the tides to find out why they happen. Now I know! It's the sun and the Quantum Moon that are mean, not Giant's Deep!</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>14</ID>
		<ParentID>13</ParentID>
		<Text>
			PLUME: Oh, Phlox... Thatch took photos of your sand dwellings and showed me once! They were beautiful. I'm sure you will grow up to be a masterful sculpter, don't you agree, Thatch?</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>15</ID>
		<ParentID>14</ParentID>
		<Text>
			THATCH: But of course... How could I have been so blind? It couldn't have been the sun, and the pull of its gravity is much stronger... <![CDATA[<i>And they're 95% composed of water!</i>]]></Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>16</ID>
		<ParentID>15</ParentID>
		<Text>
			THATCH: Phlox, I think I might finally have an answer to the cause of the mysterious <![CDATA[<color=orange>surfacing phenomenon</color>]]> thanks to your presentation!</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>17</ID>
		<ParentID>16</ParentID>
		<Text>
			THATCH: Hypothesis: The tentacled lifeforms must rise to the surface of Giant's Deep <![CDATA[<color=orange>in the presence of the Quantum Moon</color>]]> and its gravity pulling on them!</Text>
	</TextBlock>

			<TextBlock>
		<ID>18</ID>
		<ParentID>17</ParentID>
		<Text>
			THATCH: That photo of the Quantum Moon that Plume took in orbit before we landed on Giant's Deep must be what allowed us to meet the tentacled lifeforms on the surface during that first trip! It was never mere coincidence!</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>19</ID>
		<ParentID>18</ParentID>
		<Text>
			PLUME: My goodness.. You're right, Thatch! Phlox, your presentation solved this mystery we've been trying to solve since our first expedition trip... I'm so proud of you!</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>20</ID>
		<ParentID>19</ParentID>
		<Text>
			PLUME: Come, friends, we must test this hypothesis at once! Phlox, we can put away the presentation later! You should join us - let us watch the tentacled lifeforms visit the surface again together!</Text>
	</TextBlock>
			<TextBlock>
		<ID>21</ID>
		<ParentID>20</ParentID>
		<Text>
			PHLOX: Really?! Okay, papa! I want to become good friends with all of them!</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC_G R4</FactID>
			<Condition>2</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC_G R5</FactID>
			<Condition>2</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC_G EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC_G EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>2</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LC_G EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>3</Condition>
		</RevealFact>

			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SF Jelly EX1</FactID>
			<Condition>3</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SF Jelly EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>3</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>SF Jelly EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>3</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>