<DialogueTree xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://github.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/blob/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/dialogue_schema.xsd">

<NameField>Slate</NameField>

<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Slate Kids Intro</Name>
		<EntryCondition>DEFAULT</EntryCondition>
		 <SetPersistentCondition>STOWAWAY_GO_TALK_TO_KIDS</SetPersistentCondition>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Hey, hold up a sec!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		
		<DialogueOptionsList>
   			 <DialogueOption>
				<Text>What is it?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>Slate_Kids_1</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
    <DialogueOption>
				<Text>Yeah yeah yeah, I already know about the launch codes.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>Slate_Kids_2</DialogueTarget>
	</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
      			<RequiredPersistentCondition>COMPLETED_SHIPLOG_TUTORIAL</RequiredPersistentCondition>
				<Text>Use the shiplog to track places I've been to. Got it! Thank you! Seeya!</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>Slate_Kids_2</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>


	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Slate_Kids_1</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Aren't you gonna say goodbye to everyone before you take off? The whole village's gonna miss ya.</Page>
			<Page>If anything, at least say bye to the little hatchlings. All of 'em seemed to have something to ask or say to you before you go.</Page>
			<Page>Go humor 'em, just in case this is last they see of you for a while, y'know?</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Alright, alright, I'll go talk to the little gills before I go.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>Slate_Kids_Gettoit</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Where are they again?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>Slate_Kids_Direction</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

	
	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Slate_Kids_2</Name>
		<Dialogue>
		<Page>Uh, no. What are you talking about?</Page>
			<Page>I was gonna ask if you were gonna say goodbye to everyone before you take off. The whole village's gonna miss you, you know?</Page>
			<Page>If anything, at least say bye to the little hatchlings. All of 'em seemed to have something to ask or say to you before you go.</Page>
			<Page>Go humor 'em as a favor for me - just in case this is last they see of you for a while, y'know?</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Alright, alright, I'll go talk to the little gills before I go.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>Slate_Kids_Gettoit</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Where are they again?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>Slate_Kids_Direction</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Slate_Kids_Gettoit</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Cool. Just remember: there's Mica, Tephra, Galena, Arkose, and Moraine.</Page>
			<Page>If you forget to say goodbye to any one of them, they'll probably never forget it as long as they live.</Page>
			<Page>I think Mica especially had something to ask you - but they didn't want to tell me what, for whatever reason.</Page>
			<Page>I'm just saying: you probably wanna get it outta that one now. Otherwise, don't be surprised if you start seeing the model rocket flying after you with notes attached to it.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Slate_Kids_Direction</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Stars, <![CDATA[<i>I don't know!</i>]]> I'm just roasting marshmallows and relaxing here. They're hatchlings, they might have clambered into your ship somehow for all I know.</Page>
			<Page>Mica's probably still fiddling with the model rocket.</Page>
			<Page>They told me they had something to ask you they couldn't tell me for whatever reason.. So it's probably plans to steal my job or something.</Page>
				<Page>Tephra and Galena should be playing in the village somewhere.</Page>
				<Page>I saw 'em trekking outside the village recently for whatever reason, though - so don't take my word on that.</Page>
				<Page>Arkose's probably still throwing rocks into the patch of ghost matter at the top of the village.</Page>
				<Page>Still uh.. no idea why they do that all day.</Page>
					<Page>And Moraine's probably stargazing on the big tree in the village, making sure Marl doesn't chop it down.</Page>
					<Page>I wonder if that Marl'll ever let go of that grudge.</Page>
					<Page>No good in holding a grudge against a tree, you know?</Page>
						<Page>That's all I know. Just get a move on - you'll probably just find all of 'em on the way up to the observatory for those launch codes, anyway!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>



</DialogueTree>