<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Oh, Daz, look at the sunrise on Giant's Deep's horizon! I'd forgotten how short the days last on this island and Statue Island..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: And someone has even furnished <![CDATA[<color=orange>Lover's Cove</color>]]> with one of Phlox's beautiful statues! Did you transport this here, Daz?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Oh? What are you recording, my love?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		DAZ: O-oh, is this recording? I, quite meant to play us some music to unwind!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		DAZ: But, since it is already preserving our words.. I would like to say a few heartfelt words to you, my love.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		DAZ: The past few years we have spent together have been nothing short of magical.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		DAZ: Your diligence and spirit brightens my darkest days. You inspire me to innovate, iterate and appreciate details to enjoy in everything we do.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>	
	<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		DAZ: You make me feel so appreciated and loved at all times.. And I love you so, so much.
		</Text>
			</TextBlock>
				<TextBlock>	
	<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		DAZ: Cassava, will you take my appendage in marriage?
		</Text>
			</TextBlock>
				<TextBlock>	
	<ID>10</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: D-Daz, my dazzling star! Of-
		</Text>
			</TextBlock>
				<TextBlock>	
	<ID>11</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<Text>
		DAZ: YES!! I knew you'd say yes! Hypothesis confirmed! You said yes!!
		</Text>
			</TextBlock>
				<TextBlock>
		<ID>12</ID>
		<ParentID>11</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: D-Daz? I, I didn't say it yet! But yes, <![CDATA[<i>yes!</i>]]> Of course I would take your appendage in marriage!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>13</ID>
		<ParentID>12</ParentID>
		<Text>
		DAZ: The test today was a success, Cassava! AND we're engaged! Yes!!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>14</ID>
		<ParentID>13</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: I'm so confused.. And so happy!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>15</ID>
		<ParentID>14</ParentID>
		<Text>
		DAZ: I'll explain everything shortly, love! Come, let us write to our friends in the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Deep Storm Station</color>]]> through the projection wall at once!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	

<ShipLogConditions>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Cove EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>10</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>CONV R2</FactID>
			<Condition>13</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>