<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		COLEUS: Yes, yes... You're so close..!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: <![CDATA[<i>No!</i>]]> It scampered off again...
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		COLEUS: You saw the vision orb move up slightly, didn't you, Oeno? Neither of us were looking directly at the orb, were we?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		COLEUS: I've been adjusting our vision orbs to accomodate the native lifeforms' vision so they can be able to use them too. I'm quite hopeful they'll learn to use it soon!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		OENO: I wish I could credit their eyes for that, Coleus - but I'm afraid it's more likely that may have just been the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Attlerock's</color>]]> gravity tugging the vision orb upwards as it orbited overhead!
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: Was the <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Attlerock</color>]]> orbiting overhead just now? Curses.. I can't seem to get them to look at the vision orb long enough without them becoming distracted!
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Were you playing with the native lifeforms again, Coleus? You sure love teaching them more about our culture and technology!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: Of course! It's lovely seeing these lifeforms learn and grow more curious, now that they've grown much more comfortable with our presence.
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Oh, before I forget! Coleus: Yarrow was looking for you! There appears to be some issue regarding the warp towers on Ash Twin which he wanted you to look into.
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: How vague.. Did he mention what sort of problem it was?
				</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: Apparently, the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Sun Station</color>]]> crew reported to Yarrow that they noticed their warp tower's rotating doors opening and closing by themselves, without any sort of input.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>12</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>11</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CYCAD: When Yarrow went to check on the issue, he noticed the same thing happening to the rotating doors to Timber Hearth's warp tower!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>13</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>12</ParentID>
		<Text>
		COLEUS: How strange.. My thanks for delivering this message, Cycad. I shall travel to <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Ash Twin</color>]]> to catch up with Yarrow and investigate this issue as soon as I can!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	

<ShipLogConditions>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Nomai Mine Entry 2</FactID>
			<Condition>8</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>