<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text><![CDATA[<color=orange>INSPIRED PROJECT</color>]]> SCHEMATICS</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>Components: All available gravity crystals from the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Gravity Crystal Workshop,</color>]]> 1 white hole warp core.</Text>
	</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>No suitable warp cores found in Black Hole Forge (likely expended during crafting of advanced warp core..) Seeking alternatives..</Text>
		</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>Update: Suitable white hole warp core obtained from advanced warp core powering <![CDATA[<color=orange>Deep Storm Station.</color>]]></Text>
		</TextBlock>
		
	<TextBlock>	
	<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		Structure: Gravity crystals to be arranged in compact inward lattice, all surrounding and angled towards white hole warp core, with remaining external crystals used to stabilize flight trajectory.</Text>
			</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>	
	<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: The Inspired's construction was completed today.</Text>
			</TextBlock>
<TextBlock>	
	<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Using a lattice of gravity crystals arranged towards its core, the Inspired will exert a constant gravitational force to capture, compact, and pressurize all deadly matter spread across this star system.
		</Text>
			</TextBlock>
			<TextBlock>	
	<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Upon receiving the order, the central warp core will be crushed, and all comprising gravity crystals will exert a maximal force crushing inwards against the released white hole.
		</Text>
			</TextBlock>

<TextBlock>	
	<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
			 CASSAVA: The accumulated pressure will explosively release the captured matter, and deal mass destruction to any star system within blast radius.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>	
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		 CASSAVA: Once I am able to calculate the source of the comet that has stolen my clan, our future, as well as the countless lifeforms that dwelled within this star system...
		</Text>
			</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>	
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		 CASSAVA: I shall deliver to the source of this hostility - my grief, and my fury - a weapon inspired by their own.
		</Text>
			</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>INSP R3</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>INSP EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>8</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>INSP EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>