<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Ok he doesnt actl die here bc chronology but in my head he basically does</color>]]>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		YARROW: Plume, stay with us.. The shuttle should be arriving any second now.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: There was no hope after all.. I knew better, but I still wanted to hope there was a chance..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: This cold is too much for him to bear! He's becoming delirious.. We must try to warm him up however we can!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationA />
			<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: I came on this expedition in the hopes of finding any sign of survivors who had survived and escaped the bramble's mazes on Dark Bramble's exterior.. But now, I know without a shred of doubt.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationA />
			<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: Even if they had been able to escape, had they not perished to this piercing cold, stranded on a planet so far from the sun - they would surely have been swept away by Giant's Deep eventually, and perished in the vacuum of space..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationA />
			<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Plume, have hope! There is still a chance there could be survivors stowed away somewhere within Dark Bramble; we have not yet begun exploration of the bramble's vast interior yet!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationA />
			<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: How would we traverse the bramble's maze-like interior with our shuttles? Many good Nomai have already been unquestionably lost to this gruesome planet, young Cassava. We cannot risk more lives, dwelling on those we have lost..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationA />
			<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: You can only focus on those who survive, on what remains - and pave the path for those to come...
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationA />
			<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: My gratitude for your patience, Keek...
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<LocationA />
			<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<Text>
		PLUME: And my dear Phlox.. I am so sorry to leave you without saying goodbye... My gratitude for choosing me as your father...
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<LocationA />
			<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<Text>
		YARROW: Plume! Stay with us! The shuttle is almost here.. Phlox is already on his way here on the shuttle from Brittle Hollow!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>12</ID>
		<LocationA />
			<ParentID>11</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CLARY: <![CDATA[<i>The shuttle is here!</i>]]> Help us lift him to the shuttle, everyone - <![CDATA[<i>quickly!</i>]]> Plume is in urgent need of medical attention!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
</NomaiObject>