<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text><![CDATA[<color=orange>ORBITAL PROBE CANNON</color>]]> SCHEMATICS</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		Components: 3 modules connected to central chamber, with double-size gravity cannon attached to front of central module.
		</Text>
			</TextBlock>

		<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>Reminder to communciate an estimate of the amount of gravity crystals needed to power a double-size gravity cannon to the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Gravity Crystal Workshop</color>]]> on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow</color>]]> soon!</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>Each chamber is to be equipped with projection pools and whiteboards to facilitate swift communication of information between Nomai aboard each module.</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>Crafting of new projection stones for each module is to be conveyed to Daz at the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Scroll and Stone Workshop</color>]]> on Statue Island. Construction of a new warp pad to be communicated to the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Black Hole Forge.</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>	
	<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>An update: A gravity-funnel docking bay is to be installed to receive incoming shuttles instead of a warp pad, per logistical limitations of the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Black Hole Forge.</color>]]></Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>	
	<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: The warp pad to connect Giant's Deep to <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Ash Twin</color>]]> hasn't even been constructed yet, due to the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Deep Storm Station</color>]]> taking priority. Respectfully, who here was expecting us to be able to warp to the cannon?</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<ShipLogConditions>
				<RevealFact>
			<FactID>OPCSCH_EX2</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>OPCSCH_EX3</FactID>
			<Condition>3</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>OPCSCH_EX4</FactID>
			<Condition>3</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Workshop R2</FactID>
			<Condition>6</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>