<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		THATCH: I am impressed how quickly you were able to transform this island into such an impressive site, Cassava! The <![CDATA[<color=orange>Construction Yard</color>]]> looks more promising with each passing day.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: It would not have been possible without Kousa's new storm shelters keeping us safe from the cyclones - nor the hospitality of the Nomai welcoming me to this planet, Thatch!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: However, Thatch: there is one puzzling anomaly I have noticed which I must ask you about..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Have you noticed the storm shelters sometimes.. activating by themselves - even in the absence of any cyclones?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
		THATCH: Oh, so my eyes weren't mistaken! I believe I have noticed this occurence on occasion as well..
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
		THATCH: Sadly, I do not have an answer as to what could be causing this strange quirk of these storm shelters. It was not long ago we were all completely insulated from cyclones in the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Looming City,</color>]]> you see.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
		THATCH: Perhaps a visit to the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Gravity Crystal Workshop</color>]]> on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow's</color>]]> equator will shine some light on this issue. I am sure Kousa would only be happy to improve his invention!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

<ShipLogConditions>
<RevealFact>
			<FactID>INSP R2</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>INSP R1</FactID>
			<Condition>2</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
			<RevealFact>
			<FactID>GSHOP CYARD</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>