<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	
	<![CDATA[<color=orange>Excavation Site</color>]]>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Time is running short. Dawn will break shortly on Timber Hearth, and rouse the native lifeforms from their rest.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: I believe I have drawn as much of the deadly matter from the planet's surface onto the Inspired as I am able. Concentrations have now reached an undetectable level on much of the planet.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: After careful calculation and execution of an additional orbit of the Inspired across the star system, I believe I have also siphoned as much of the remaining stagnant deadly matter as I am safely able to.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: However, narrow spaces and caverns deep underground remain beyond the reach of the Inspired's gravitational influence.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: In particular, <![CDATA[<color=orange>mining site 2b on Timber Hearth</color>]]>  remains dangerously irradiated, and still poses a great threat to the native species.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: To protect the native species from the danger of their own curiosity, I have therefore used a <![CDATA[<color=orange>scroll to seal the locking mechanism of the entrance</color>]]> into the mines.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Though rudimentary, I pray it will hold and serve its purpose to contain the matter within, until its danger is tempered by time.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: My dearest hope is that the native species of this star system will live on to explore and learn more from the universe.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: Now, there is only the remaining task of containing the deadly matter.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: ... I am ready.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: In my final moments, I am filled with gratitude and admiration for all that I have been able to learn and experience.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>12</ID>
		<ParentID>11</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: The universe I was born within, and the tiny window of its life that I glimpsed - has inspired boundless curiosity in me, with both its vast terror and vast beauty...
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>13</ID>
		<ParentID>12</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>
		CASSAVA: May the universe to come... receive me swiftly!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


<ShipLogConditions>
	<RevealFact>
			<FactID>Deep Storm Station ENTERED</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>INSP R4</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>

</NomaiObject>