<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>MALLOW: My love, have you seen the shuttle flying to Giant's Deep repeatedly? Whatever could be happening to compel so many flight attempts?</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>AVENS: It appears they are attempting to land on the north pole of the planet... Could it be some younglings beginning their quantum pilgrimage?</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<LocationA />
		<Text>AVENS: How strange. It should not be that hard to calculate a shuttle trajectory to the north pole, should it?</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<LocationB />
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>MALLOW: <![CDATA[<b>OH.</b>]]> I remember now! It's that awful <![CDATA[<color=orange>landing pad</color>]]> on the northern island that tests younglings on pinpoint-accurate shuttle calculations!</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>AVENS: What? I was only taught it was a mechanism of some kind to conserve on power.. I only recall mustering my courage to ask you if we could take the shuttle to Giant's Deep together that day..</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>	
	<ID>6</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>MALLOW: The shuttle has to land on the <![CDATA[<color=orange>landing pad</color>]]> in order to power the tractor beam to ascend the tower. Otherwise, there's no way to enter the tower.</Text>
			</TextBlock>
				<TextBlock>	
	<ID>7</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>MALLOW: And <![CDATA[<i>I</i>]]> recall you accidentally recalling the shuttle back to the gravity cannon, after I landed us perfectly on the landing pad... Oh, you were <![CDATA[<i>fortunate</i>]]> I didn't calculate a shuttle trajectory into the <![CDATA[<i>sun</i>]]> for us afterwards.</Text>
			</TextBlock>
				<TextBlock>	
	<ID>8</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>AVENS: I'm sure we could have just used a sufficiently heavy boulder to weigh down the landing pad, as my brother and his soon-to-be spouse did. Hah, I pray he lands <![CDATA[<i>that</i>]]> shuttle on the northern landing pad!</Text>
			</TextBlock>
				<TextBlock>	
	<ID>9</ID>
		<LocationA />
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>MALLOW: <![CDATA[<i>Ugh,</i>]]> is that where that phrase comes from? And don't even joke about Cassava in that way - he already knows about this secret wall we use!!</Text>
			</TextBlock>
</NomaiObject>